A Guide to the World War II Panoramic Photographs 1941-1944
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
World War II Panoramic Photographs 1941-1944
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
11503
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Contents List
- "Somewhere in Carolina": a souvenir picture. Army Maneuvers of 1941 (Dietz Press, Richmond, Virginia, copyright W.R. Thompson & Company, Publishers, Richmond, Virginia) 1941
  Depicts, planes, dirigibles, parachute drops, artillery, trucks, tanks, cavalry, motorcycle units, soldiers in column, and a camp, all being watched by an African-American farm family and field workers.
- Camp Lee, Virginia, 1941, Dietz Press, Richmond, Virginia, copyright W.R. Thompson & Company, Publishers, Richmond, Virginia 1941
  Aerial view of the barracks with planes flying overhead in formation.
- Company D, 4th Engineer Training Battalion, Engineer Replacement Training Center, Fort Belvoir, Virginia, names of men printed on the photograph 1942
- Fort Eustis, Virginia, View from the Central Water Tower (Dietz Press, Richmond, Virginia, copyright W.R. Thompson & Company, Publishers) 1941
- Battery C, 2nd C.A. Training Battalion, Fort Eustis, Virginia, with names of the men printed on the photograph, by Stieg, Washington, D.C. Dec 1941
- 4th Platoon, C Company, 1st Battalion, Engineer Replacement Training Center, Ft. Belvoir, Virginia Apr 25 1942
- Company A, 8th Quartermaster Training Regiment, Camp Lee, Virginia, names of men listed on photograph by platoon, with officers listed separately, photographer Washington Photography Company Feb 17 1942
- Company K, 7th Quartermaster Training Regiment, Camp Lee, Virginia, names of men listed on photograph by platoon, with officers listed separately, photographer Washington Photography Company Oct 1942
- Company D, 4th Engineers Battalion, Engineer Replacement Training Center, Fort Belvoir, Virginia, with each platoon also photographed separately Jan 1944
- Battery C, 2nd C.A. Training Battalion, Fort Eustis, has names of men on photograph.
- Battery C, 7th C.A. Training Battalion, Fort Eustis, Virginia, Jan. 1942 (Steig, Wash., D.C.), a group photograph, with names; also includes four small inset photographs of scenes at Fort Eustis.